Guide to the Columbia Unoversity Press Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Office Files
  - Files: Suryeys & reorganizations, 1947-1950 (Box 261)
  - Finances, 1923-1947 (Box 261)
  - Financial reports, 1932 (Box 261)
  - Financial reports: departments, 1943-1950 (Box 261)
  - Floor space, 1930-1946 (Box 263)
  - Floor space - stockroom, 1948-1953 (Box 263)
  - Foreign sales, 1946-1956 (Box 263)
  - History of Press (Box 263)
  - I -miscellaneous, 1931 (Box 263)
  - In press, 1949-1951 (Box 263)
  - Incorporation, 1893; 1931-1937 (Box 263)
  - Industrial surveys, 1947-1949 (Box 263)
  - Insurance - Associated Hospital Service of New York, 1945-1947 (Box 263)
  - Insurance - Group Health Insurance, Inc., 1945-1951 (Box 263)
  - Insurance - Group Life Insurance, 1942-1949 (Box 263)
  - Insurance - information, 1944-1952 (Box 263)
  - Insurance - misc., 1936-1948 (Box 263)
  - Insurance - T.I.A.A., 1935-1946 (Box 263)
  - Inventories of equipment, 1950-1952 (Box 263)
  - King's Crown Press, 1940-1948 (Box 263)
  - King's Crown Press - distribution schedules, 1947/1948 (Box 263)
  - Legal affairs, 1930-1950 (Box 263)
  - Library, 1931 (Box 263)
  - Monthly operating statements, 1951-1955 (Box 263)
  - Monthly sales for Hamlin, Gazetteer, Columbia Encyclopedia, & Grange, 1950-1956 (Box 263)
  - NRA Codes - National Recovery Act: Codes for book manufacturing, 1933/1934 (Box 263)
  - Office management - memoranda, 1932-1945 (Box 263)
  - Office management - purchase orders, 1948-1955 (Box 263)
  - Office space, 1931 (Box 263)
  - Parcel post insurance, 1948-1952 (Box 264)
  - Periodicals, 1948 (Box 264)
  - Personnel - Government regulations, 1942-1945 (Box 264)
  - Personnel - hours, 1934-1953 (Box 264)
  - Personnel - students, 1934 (Box 264)
  - Physical working conditions, 1940-1953 (Box 264)
  - Printing department, 1936-1947 (Box 264)
  - Prize contests, 1938 (Box 264)
  - Production department, 1940-1948 (Box 264)
  - Proffitt, Charles G., 1921 (Box 264)
  - Public relations, 1946-1952 (Box 264)
  - Publication Committee, 1929-1943 (Box 264)
  - Publication service to other organizations, 1941 (Box 264)
  - Publishing funds needed, 1949-1953 (Box 264)
  - Publishing policies and procedures, 1933-1950 (Box 264)
  - Real estate, 1926 (Box 264)
  - Receipts, 1926-1921 (Box 264)
  - Recreational activities, 1946-1949 (Box 264)
  - Remainders, 1934-1951 (Box 264)
  - Sales analyses, 1947-1950 (Box 264)
  - Sales and advertising department, 1938-1945 (Box 264)
  - Summary weekly reports, 1954-1956 (Box 264)
  - Sales figures, 1927-1941 (Box 264)
  - Sales reports, 1895-1959 (Box 264)
  - Scholarly editions - notes on costs & methods, 1946-1949 (Box 265)
  - Selective service & reserves, 1942-1951 (Box 265)
  - Special reports for Charles G. Proffitt, 1950-1955 (Box 265)
  - Stock department, 1937-1946 (Box 265)
  - Textbooks, 1947-1951 (Box 265)
  - Trustees meetings - minutes, 1893-1912, ((Xerox copy & microfilm copy)) (Box 265)
  - Trustees meetings - minutes, 1913-1922, ((Xerox copy & microfilm copy)) (Box 266)
  - Trustees meetings, 1923-1926, ((Xerox copy)) (Box 265)
  - Trustees meetings - correspondence & annual report, 1942-1944 (Box 265)
  - Trustees meetings - correspondence & annual report, 1945-1949 (Box 267)
  - Trustees meetings - annual report, 1951/1952 (Box 267)
  - Typesetting departments, 1930-1945 (Box 267)
  - U.S, Customs, 1934-1938 (Box 267)
  - U.S. Library of Congress - Copyright Office, 1923-1924 (Box 267)
  - U.S National Production Authority, 1951 (Box 267)
  - U.S. Office of Price Administration, 1943 (Box 267)
  - U.S. War Production Board - Priorities, 1942-1943 (Box 267)
  - University Service Bureau, 1931-1953 (Box 267)
  - Workmens' Compensation Insurance, 1946-1947 (Box 267)
- Series IV: Columbia University Press - Printed Materials
  - Columbia University Press General Cata1og, 1893-1972, (One volume ) (Box 268)
  - Announcements - General, 1947-1953 (Box 268)
  - Announcements - International Documents Service, 1947-1953 (Box 268)
  - Catalogues, 1946-1948 (Box 268)
  - Catalogues, 1948-1950 (Box 268)
  - Catalogues, 1950-1953 (Box 268)
  - Publicity - Miscellaneous, 1947-1953 (Box 268)